

# CHRISTIANNA ANASTASIADOU

- Aspiring Web Developer -

### CONTACT

- +30 6982796097
- c.anastasiadou@hotmail.com
- Petroupoli, Athens, Greece
- github.com/Starfoxx-21
- in linkedin.com/in/christiannaanastasiadou

## **SOFT SKILLS**

- Organized
- Teamwork
- Detailed-focused
- Time Management

#### LANGUAGE

Greek •••••

English •••••

### **INTERESTS**

- Drawing
- Playing Video Games
- Traveling
- Skiing
- Learning Programming Languages

## PERSONAL WEBSITE

https://starfoxx-21.github.io/

## **SUMMARY**

I am a self-taught frontend developer transitioning from a 4-year career in accounting. My background has equipped me with strong problem-solving skills, a detail-oriented mindset, and the ability to learn and adapt quickly. Over the past year, I have been building my knowledge in HTML, CSS, and JavaScript, and I am currently learning React. I am excited to apply my technical skills and passion for continuous learning in a junior developer role.

## **SKILLS**

Familiar with: HTML, CSS, Javascript, Python, MySQL

Frameworks: Bootstrap, Tailwind CSS

Currently learning: React

Experimented with: Astro

# **WORK EXPERIENCE**

Jun 2024 - Nov 2024

## Campeón Gaming

Junior Accounting Executive

Sep 2022 - May 2024

#### **CG Elenxis IKE**

**Junior Accountant** 

Jan 2021 - Aug 2022

#### SafeTaxPlan

Assistant Accountant

# **EDUCATION**

Sept 2016 - Sept 2020

University of West Attica - Degree in Accounting and Finance

Bachelor of Business Administration - BBA

Sept 2013 - Sept 2016

1st Technical High School of Petroupoli - Accounting/ Economics